>> Jem Young: 所以我之前教了 IP 表，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So
I previously have taught about IP tables,
是路由，阻塞或
which are ways of routing, blocking, or
拒绝某些端口对某些协议的请求。
denying requests to certain
ports over certain protocols.
但他们真的很麻烦
But they're really onerous.
如果你不能在这里说，这不是一个非常友好的语法。
And if you can't tell here,
it's not a very friendly syntax.
幸运的是开放软件基金会和 Ubuntu 的那种人
Fortunately the kind people at the Open
Software Foundation and Ubuntu and
Linux和互联网上的优秀公民创造了一些东西
Linux, and just the good citizens of
the Internet, created something a little
更轻量的称为 ufw ，不复杂的防火墙。
bit more lightweight called ufw,
the uncomplicated firewall.
如果你不能说，这一不复杂的防火墙将会变得不那么复杂。
If you can't tell, this uncomplicated
firewall will be much less complicated.
再次，防火墙仅控制对这些端口的访问
And again, a firewall just controls
the access to these ports and
能从你电脑里出来的人
who can get in and out of your computer.
>> Jem Young: 与 IP 表不同， ufw 的语法更简单
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And unlike IP tables,
ufw has a much simpler syntax for
基本服务。
basic services.
因此，如果我拒绝说 HPS 的话，我可以说，我可以否认 HPS。
So if I want to deny say
HPS I can say ufw deny HPS.
当你在表面上思考的时候
And it's much easier to reason about when
you're think about on a surface level
而不是端口级别。
rather than a port level.
我不需要这样想我也不用想
And I don't have to be like,
I don't have to think,
我要阻止所有 TCP 流量到端口 4430。
I want to block all TCP
traffic to port 4430.
不，我只能说 UFW 否认 HPS ，它会阻止所有流量到端口 443。
No, I can just say UFW deny HPS, and
it's gonna block all traffic to port 443.
所以现在它没有在运行。
So right now it's not running.
因为你知道我想要什么吗 ?
So let's get it up and
running because you know what I want?
我要关闭 3000 口，对。
I want to close port 3000, yes.
>> 扬声器 2: 拒绝和拒绝之间有什么区别 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What's the difference
between deny and reject?
>> Jem Young: 大问题。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Great question.
我不知道我能不能再考虑一下吗 如果没有的话我马上就来
I wonder if I cover that later?
If not, I'll cover right now.
所以否认是，我在努力记住这一差异。
So deny is,
I'm trying to remember the difference.
拒绝黑洞请求，好的，它不响应请求。
Deny black holes requests, okay,
it doesn't respond to requests.
所以如果我想进入港口我不知道 47号我能 ping 到那个港口
So if I'm trying to get into port, I don't
know, 47, I can just ping that port or
尝试访问它，它会挂起来，它会挂起来挂起来。
try to access it, it'll just hang,
it'll just hang and hang.
但我已经放弃了这一要求
But internally I've already
dropped that request.
我什么都没做但我不会明确回应港口是封闭的
I didn't do anything about it, but I won't
respond explicitly that port is closed.
拒绝说明， hey，此端口已关闭，并将包发送回服务器。
Reject says, hey, this port is closed,
and it sends a packet back to the server.
有时候你想明确告诉别人
The difference is sometimes you wanna
be explicit about telling people that
端口是关闭的，或者类似您使用错误端口的端口，或者
the port is closed, or something
like you're using the wrong port, or
您正在尝试访问错误的服务器。
you're trying to access the wrong server.
你想成为那些试图使用你服务的人的好公民
You wanna be a good citizen to
the people trying to use your service.
当你想黑洞的时候
Other times you wanna black hole them and
别让他们告诉他们发生了什么
not let them tell them anything
about what's happening.
你不知道那港口是开放的还是只是花了很长时间来回应
You don't know if that port's open or if
it's just taking a long time to respond or
任何事
anything.
通常你总是想要黑洞的要求除非你有特定的情况
Generally you always wanna black hole
requests, unless you have a specific case
当你想告诉人们你想进入的服务是
when you wanna tell people that the
service that you're trying to access is
不正确或参数无效或类似的情况。
incorrect or the parameters are invalid or
something like that.
但我很惊讶他们没把它放进去
Great question though, I'm surprised
they didn't put it in there, and
我可以后退，等待，否，拒绝或拒绝，是。
I could have it backwards,
wait, no, deny or reject, yes.
像刚才我们在 ping 的一个例子
A lot like the example we gave
earlier when we're trying to ping
frontendmasters.com 和它的挂断。
frontendmasters.com and
it just hangs and hangs.
这是一种好的方式，我会说放慢袭击者的速度。
That's a good way of kind of,
I'll say slowing down attackers.
我不想否认袭击者的身份因为他们会得到的
I don't wanna say deny attackers
because they'll get around that.
但是每次尝试去吃资源都是好办法
But it's good way of kind of eating
resources cuz every time they try to
连接到一个只黑洞的服务它只会挂起和挂起
connect to a service that just black
holes them, it just hangs and hangs and
它会吃掉他们的电脑资源，它会减慢他们的爬行速度。
it eats their computer resources,
it kind of slows down their port crawling.
Versus 拒绝明确表示您不允许执行此操作。
Versus reject which is explicitly
saying you're not allowed to do that.
问得好
Great question though.
>> Jem Young: 所以已安装了 ufw ，但它可能未在运行，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: So ufw's installed but
it may not be running,
但我们还是去看看吧
but let's check it out.
因此， sudo ufw 状态， >> Jem Young: 它处于不活动状态。
So sudo ufw status,
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: It's inactive.
所以我想说苏多开始吧
So I'm gonna say sudo ufw start,
should do it.
它不启用。
It does not enable.
我一直这么做
I always do that.
sudo ufw 启用。
sudo ufw enable.
>> Jem Young: 这可能会中断我的现有 SSH 连接，
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And this may interrupt
my existing SSH connection,
所以我们只能说 " 是"
so we're just gonna say yes.
>> Jem Young: 我们很棒。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And we're good.
我再给你说一次当你开始安全的时候
I'll say this for you ufw, again,
when you start getting into security and
IP 表和路由， ufw有点容易。
IP tables and routing,
ufw's a little bit easier.
但你完全可以把自己关在服务器之外。
But you can absolutely lock
yourself out of the server.
如果关闭端口 22 ( 这是我的 SSH 端口 ) ，我无法进入服务器
If I close port 22, which is my SSH port,
I have no way of getting into the server
在那个时候我被关了所以很小心
at that point and I'm locked out,
so be very careful.
好吧你可能不会做什么坏事
ufw's okay, you're probably not
gonna do anything too bad, but
如果您开始拒绝 SSH 请求或将其黑色保留在其中，
if you start rejecting SSH requests or
black holeing them in,
你会在一个受伤的世界里无法进入服务器
you'll be in a world of hurt cuz there's
no way to get in the server that point
因为港口已经关闭了它就在某个地方被锁住了
because the port is closed,
it's literally locked up somewhere.
>> Jem Young: 但是我们允许 SSH ，所以我们没问题。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: But
we allowed SSH, so we're okay.
因此，让我们再次运行 ufw 状态以查看打开的内容。
So let's run ufw status
again to see what's open.
所以 sudo ufw 状态应该已启动并正在运行，并且它正在运行。
So sudo ufw status should be up and
running, and it's running.
>> Jem Young: 让我们找到命令，告诉我什么是路径
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: And let's find the command
to show me what is the routes
他们在跑你的防火墙状态是什么
they're running,
what's your firewall status?
让我们说状态详细。
Let's say status verbose.
>> Jem Young: 没有，现在我们还可以，因为我们
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Nothing, so
right now we're still okay because we
完全没把自己关起来
didn't lock ourselves out completely.
但我要确保我有这个规则所以 sudo ufw 允许 ssh
But I'm just gonna make sure I had
a rule for this, so sudo ufw allow ssh.
现在，当我上去的时候，我们看到我们为现在的 SSH 添加了一个规则。
Now when I do go up, we see that
we added a rule for SSH for now.
当你打开状态时它就会打开
It stays open because
when you turn on ufw,
缺省情况下，不会阻塞 SSH 端口，因为它们知道如果已启用
by default it's not gonna block your SSH
port because they know that if you enabled
当你在你的服务器上你就被开除了然后你就被关了
it when you're on your server you get
kicked out and then you locked out.
幸运的是有人试图让事情变得更容易些
Fortunately, there are people that they
try to make things a little bit easier
给你的
for you.
我们想让一些其他的事情，或者其实，对不起，
We want to enable a few other things,
or actually, sorry,
我们都没做过
we didn't actually enable it.
或者没有，我们已经做到了。
Or no, we did already enable it.
我想允许其他的事情所以我想允许 HTTP
Well I wanna allow a few other things,
so I wanna allow HTTP.
因此 sudo ufw 允许 htp ，并且您再次授予状态，
So sudo ufw allow htp, and
you grant status again,
我们看到了防火墙的状态
and we see the status of our firewall.
这是一个比 IP 表更友好的语法。
This is a much, much,
much friendlier syntax than IP tables.
我不知道你们有没有做过 IP 表的事
[LAUGH] I don't know if any of you have
ever done anything with IP tables,
但他们根本不友善，一旦你仁慈了就会有道理
but they are not friendly at all,
and they make sense once you kind
了解语法和所发生的事情
of understand the syntax and
what's happening.
但是， ufw 只是一个很好的包装器，一个环绕 IP 表的清洁包装器。
But ufw is just a nice wrapper,
a clean wrapper around IP tables.
>> Jem Young: 是的，这只是展示状态，对。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah,
that's just showing status, yes.
>演讲者 3: 我们将允许  和
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: We're gonna allow HTTPS and
然后使用 Nginx 将所有 HTTP 流量重定向到 ?
then use Nginx to redirect all
the HTTP traffic to HTTPS?
> > Jem Young: 是的，你在向前跳。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yes, you're jumping ahead.
不没关系的
[LAUGH] No, it's okay.
我们最终会打开  端口，那就是 443 端口，
We will eventually, we're gonna open
the HTTPS port, so that's port 443,
当我们打开 的时候
when we turn on HTTPS.
那一会儿就会发生了
And that'll happen a little bit later.
所以用 ufw 不看，我怎么创造
So using ufw without it looking it up,
how would I create
要阻止所有 HTTP 连接的规则吗 ?
a rule to block all HTTP
connections if I wanted to?
这不是什么把戏
It's not a trick?
>> Jem Young: 任何人，别让我打电话给你。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Anybody,
don't make me call on you.
>> 扬声器 4:ufw 拒绝?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: ufw reject?
>> Jem Young: 是的，拒绝什么?
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, reject what?
>> 演讲者 4: HTTP。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: HTTP.
>> Jem Young: 对，没什么。
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: Yeah, nothing to it.
这就是为什么它被称为不复杂的防火墙。
And that's why it's called
the uncomplicated firewall.
它只是简化了防火墙
It just simplifies your firewall and
它让我们很容易明白发生了什么
it makes it really easy to
understand what's happening.
>> Jem Young: sudo 拒绝 http， nice.
&gt;&gt; Jem Young: sudo reject http, nice.